Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Newsletter Collection, 1910-2005 RL.00733
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Clark, Earle. Discussion of Business Policies Appropriate to Present Economic Conditions 1923 Nov.
Clark, Earle. What Will Your Business Policies Be in 1923? 1923 Jan.
Cody, E. Morrill. Advertising Adventures in France 1923 June
Cunningham, Janet. New Types for Old? 1929 Oct.
David, Donald Kirk. Aims and Responsibilities of the Business School 1927 Mar.
Day, William L.. Can Advertising Cripple Manufacturing and Selling Resourcefulness? 1929 Aug.
Day, William L.. Sales and Advertising Problems of Merged Industries 1929 Mar.
Day, William L.. Vogue and Volume 1928 Nov.
De Vries, John T.. Character and Unity from Hidden Technique 1922 Mar.
De Vries, John T.. Eloquence in Advertising Illustration 1922 Feb.
Dodge, Astrid. Work of an Advertising Kitchen 1922 Sept.
Dunne, Richard A.. What Is the Trend in the Use of Color? 1925 July
Faulkner, George H.. ...And You Meet Such Interesting People 1930 Apr.
Flinn, Richard A.. State Labor Bureau Index as a Guide to Purchasing Power 1924 Mar.
Flower, H.C.. Ambassadors of Commerce 1930 Apr.
Fowler, George S.. Sanuel Reyburn Discusses Man-Power in Business 1927 Jan.
Fowler, George S.. When the Chain Store Puts Its Wrong Foot Foremost 1926 Jan.
Freyd, Max. Finding the Peak of Drawing Power 1923 Aug.
Fuller, Edward. When Will Air Transportation Arrive? 1930 May
Groom, William S.. Use of Dealer Electros in Merchandising 1922 May
Groom, William S.. What Makes Turnover and What it Means 1923 Apr.
Gwinn, Ralph W.. Why the Chain Store? 1929 Mar.
Hale, J. Mark. Value of Recipes in Advertising 1923 Aug.
Harcourt, Alfred. Changing Markets 1930 May
Hartzell, A.E.. Give a Thought to Spain 1928 Mar.
Hartzell, A.E.. When Carmen Goes Shopping-- 1928 July
Henderson, Howard. Behind the Doorbell 1923 Aug.
Henson, H. Hensley. Truth, Commerce, and World Peace 1924 Oct.
Holmes, Mildred. Bunk 1929 Aug.
Holmes, Mildred. Housewives Write the Copy 1923 May
Hoover, Herbert. Reducing the Cost of Distribution 1925 Feb.
Hutchison, James L.. Brass Tacks in Foreign Trade 1923 Feb.
Hutchison, James L.. Complex Art of Being Simple 1923 Mar.
Hutchison, James L.. Modern Advertising Methods in China 1922 Aug.
Johnson, Peirce. Getting the Most Out of Color 1922 June
Kennedy, William D.. Reader Advertisement 1928 Nov.
Kilbourn, Orrin P.. New Era in the Automobile Industry 1928 Nov.
Kinney, Gilbert. Full Dinner Pail Idea Kept the Republicans in for Sixteen Years 1924 Oct.
Kinney, Gilbert. How to Get Prestige for American Products 1926 June
Kinney, Gilbert. How to Sell Salesmen on Advertising 1922 June
Kinney, Gilbert. Loyalties in the Making 1923 Jan.
Kinney, Gilbert. Now That The Excess Profits Tax Has Gone--? 1922 Apr.
Kinney, Gilbert. What is Fair? 1926 Sept.
Kinney, Gilbert. What Manner of Man--! 1923 May
Klein, Julius. Planned Prosperity 1930 Apr.
Kohl, Howard. Getting Advertising Produced 1922 Apr.
Leffingwell, Albert. Coue Was Right 1923 May
Leffingwell, Albert. Gentle Reader 1922 May
Leffingwell, Albert. Practical Appeal in Advertising to Men 1924 Dec.
Leffingwell, Albert. They Don't Want to Read It! 1922 Nov.
Legler, Henry. Association Advertising 1929 Apr.
Lewander, Gosta M.. International Trade as a Promoter of Peace 1930 May
Lewis, Edith. Emotional Quality in Advertisements 1923 Apr.
Maule, Frances. How to Get a Good Consumer Image 1922 Mar.
Maule, Frances. Snob Appeal 1923 Mar.
Maule, Frances. Woman Appeal 1924 Jan.
Mazur, Paul. Advertising and American Prosperity 1928 May
Mazur, Paul. Is the Cost of Distribution Too High? 1925 Dec.
Mazur, Paul. Logic of the Department Store Organization 1925 Sept.
McCabe, Thomas B.. How I Selected an Advertising Agency (Scott) 1929 Oct.
McKenna, Reginald. American Dollar Replaces the Gold Standard 1928 Mar.
Meek, Samuel. Few Facts About Our Work Abroad 1928 Nov.
Mehren, Edward J.. How Should the Advertiser Measure the Value of a Business Paper? 1925 July
Miller, George L.. What Does an Automobile Dealer Mean by Service? 1922 May
Mims, Stewart L.. Importance of Investigation to an Agency and Its Clients 1922 June
Mims, Stewart L.. You Don't Know a Damn Thing About Raincoats 1922 Mar.
Miner, Henry C.. American Manufacturer Meets His Foreign Consumer 1929 Oct.
Miner, Henry J.. Major Difficulties in Asia Minor 1928 July
O'Meara, Walter. On a Phase of Copy Style 1924 Dec.
O'Shea, Monica B.. Familiar Human Material Doing a New Job 1929 Oct.
Paradise, S.H.. Improvement in British Conditions 1922 Oct.
Paradise, S.H.. London-Paris Air Line 1922 Feb.
Paradise, S.H.. Oh, But We Are Different 1923 Nov.
Parker, Dorothy. Chicago Office Goes Pyrenees 1929 Dec.
Pearson, George. Elementary Methods in Selecting Newspaper Media 1922 June
Perkins, Frederick. Packages 1922 Apr.
Perrin, E.O.. Development of Outdoor Advertising 1922 Feb.
Perrin, E.O.. Effectiveness of Various Sizes of Advertising Space 1922 Oct.
Posey, Chester A.. Unusual Achievement in the Paint Industry 1922 Aug.
Raymond, C.E.. Development of Advertising With Distribution 1922 Oct.
Resor, Stanley. Advertising as an Career 1927 May
Resor, Stanley. Dollar-A-Year Graduate School 1929 Aug.
Resor, Stanley. How Do Current Changes in the Field of Distribution Affect the Practice of Advertising? 1925 Dec.
Resor, Stanley. How Important are Store Demonstrations and Special Commissions to Clerks? 1923 Mar.
Resor, Stanley. Introduction [to issue on advertising abroad] 1928 July
Resor, Stanley. New Information 1924 July
Resor, Stanley. Personalities and the Public: Some Aspects of Testimonial Advertising 1929 Apr.
Resor, Stanley. What Do These Changes Mean? 1923 Dec.
Resor, Stanley. What Does the College Man Mean to Advertising? 1928 May
Resor, Stanley. What Your Community Must Do Before Advertising 1925 Aug.
Resor, Stanley. What the American Association of Advertising Agencies Does to Make Advertising cientifically More Effective 1924 Dec.
Richey, S. Hunter. One Best Answer for Every Sales Resistance 1923 Feb.
Richey, S. Hunter. Timing Intensive Selling with Advertising 1922 Aug.
Ricketts, William. What Does South America Offer the American Advertiser? 1928 July
Rivers, Stuart. I Want a... 1923 Feb.
Rothschild, Richard. Using Waste Circulation to Sell the Product 1922 Aug.
Smith, Guy C.. Advertising Manager--A Business Man or Technician? 1929 Dec.
Smith, Harlan. American Farmer, Inc. 1922 Oct.
Stanton, Henry T.. Advertising and the Cost of Distribution 1927 June
Stanton, Henry T.. Two Examples 1922 Sept.
Swope, Gerard. Responsibilities of Modern Industry 1927 Jan.
Thompson, Clyde S.. Trend in Outdoor Advertising 1930 Apr.
Tipper, Harry. General Motors Around the World 1928 Mar.
Tomlinson, W.P.. What Price Progress? 1927 Apr.
Townsend, Dorothy. Mrs. Wilkins Reads the Ladies Home Journal 1923 June
Waldo, Ruth. Invention--The Essence of Advertising 1929 Dec.
Walker, David N.. Do Your Salesmen Use Your Advertising? 1923 Aug.
Walker, David N.. Great American Cupboard 1923 Nov.
Watson, Clement H.. Markets are People--Not Places 1928 July
Watson, John B.. Advertising By Radio 1923 May
Watson, John B.. Are Booklets Read and Kept? 1922 Sept.
Watson, John B.. Just a Piece of Key Copy 1929 Aug.
Watson, John B.. Personality and the Choice of Personnel (II): Can Psychology Help in the Selection of Personnel? 1927 Apr.
Watson, John B.. Personality and the Choice of Personnel (II): The Behaviorist Looks at Personality 1927 Mar.
Watson, John B.. Thinking as Viewed By the Behaviorists 1927 Feb.
Watson, John B.. What Cigarette Are You Smoking and Why? 1922 July
Watson, Richmond. Polling the Consumer 1930 May
Webb, Ewing T.. Cutting Down Waste in Store Display 1922 May
Webb, Ewing T.. Largest National Expense: How Advertising Helps Reduce It 1922 Mar.
Wengler, Harold. Transmuting and Delivering a Bowl of Cereal (Hot) 1929 Aug.
Willey and Locock. Report on Visit to the United States of America 1926 Apr.
Winslow, Emma A.. Contributions from Budget Studies to the Construction of a Statistical Index of the Purchasing Power of Consumers in the United States 1924 Mar.
Woolf, James D.. Problem of Creating Desire 1922 Apr.
Wyman, Walter A.. Are American Manufacturers Foolish Exporters? 1922 Dec.
Young, James W.. Control of the Advertising Appropriation 1922 Feb.
Young, James W.. Co-operative Advertising 1926 Nov.
Unattributed. 2nd Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art 1922 Nov.
Unattributed. A House in the Country 1922 May
Unattributed. Achievements of the Automobile 1925 Aug.
Unattributed. Advertising Principles Applied to International Politics 1925 Jan.
Unattributed. Advertising Revenue Twice That from Subscription Sales 1925 Mar.
Unattributed. American Manufacturers Find a Market in Lithuania 1924 Jan.
Unattributed. Analysis of Building Volume 1923 Feb.
Unattributed. Ancient Art and Modern Industry 1922 Apr.
Unattributed. Art Sources Investigated 1923 Apr.
Unattributed. At Last--A Boon to the Inventor 1922 Aug.
Unattributed. Automobile Registrations Jump Two Millions in 1924 1925 Feb.
Unattributed. Automobile Saturation? 1926 July
Unattributed. Beech-Nut Case 1922 Feb.
Unattributed. Bertand Russell on Behaviorism 1927 Jan.
Unattributed. Bit of Old New England in a New York Office Building 1925 Jan.
Unattributed. Britain Now Has 562 Millionaires 1928 May
Unattributed. British Courts Render Interesting Decision on Advertising 1928 May
Unattributed. British Papers Boost Their Circulation With Free Insurance 1922 June
Unattributed. Brooklyn Retailers Seek Court Order to Compel Push-Cart Vendors to Trade in ront of Their Stores 1925 Sept.
Unattributed. C.M. Olmstead Joins the Staff 1923 Apr.
Unattributed. Cement Shortage Threatens 1922 Nov.
Unattributed. [Cherington] Will Head Subcommittee on Census of Distribution 1927 Apr.
Unattributed. Clients of the J. Walter Thompson Company 1922 (Mar., May, July, Sept., Nov.); 1923 (Jan., Mar., May, July, Nov.); 1924 (Jan., July, Oct.); 1925 (July-Oct., Dec.); 1926 (Jan., Apr., June, July, Sept., Nov.); 1927 (Jan.-June, Sept.); 1928 (Mar., May, July, Nov.); 1929 (Mar., Apr., Aug., Dec.); 193
Unattributed. Columnist Views Modern Merchandising 1927 Sept.
Unattributed. Come Back of the Auto Industry 1922 Aug.
Unattributed. Competition of Canadian and American Magazines in Canada 1923 Apr.
Unattributed. Consumers Decide 1926 July
Unattributed. Consumer's Purchasing Power in Thirty-one Cities 1924 Nov.
Unattributed. Contestants Busy on Essay 1923 Jan.
Unattributed. Convention of the A.A.C. of W. 1923 July
Unattributed. Department Store Costs of Business 1922 Oct.
Unattributed. Distinguished British Physician Tells of Progress in the Mastery of Disease 1924 Nov.
Unattributed. Do Busy Men Read Advertisements? 1922 June
Unattributed. Dr, Klein Optimistic as to Export Market 1926 Sept.
Unattributed. Exhibition of Home Furnishings 1922 Oct.
Unattributed. Fordized Distribution 1927 May
Unattributed. Foreign Trade of U,S, Shows a Substantial Increase 1925 Oct.
Unattributed. General Practitioner to Stay But Will Have to Work With Research Laboratories 1925 Sept.
Unattributed. Growth of Canadian Magazines 1923 Aug.
Unattributed. Growth of Chain Drug Stores 1922 June
Unattributed. Harlan Smith Comes to J. Walter Thompson Company 1922 Sept.
Unattributed. Harvard Advertising Awards 1925 Mar.
Unattributed. Headquarters of Some of the J. Walter Thompson Foreign Offices 1928 Mar.
Unattributed. How a Rubber Mat Revolutionized a Nation's Footwear Habits 1922 Aug.
Unattributed. How Many Consumers Are Necessary for the Support of a Store? 1925 Jan.
Unattributed. How Many Homes Does Magazine Advertising Reach? 1925 Jan.
Unattributed. How Strong Are the Chain Drug Stores in the Larger Cities? 1926 July
Unattributed. How Strong Are the Chain Groceries in the Leading Cities 1926 June
Unattributed. I Spend Half My Life in the Kitchen 1925 Jan.
Unattributed. Increase in Population Will Demand Cheaper Food 1922 Nov.
Unattributed. Is the Chain Store Still In Its Infancy? 1925 July
Unattributed. J. Walter Thompson Prize Essay Contest 1924 Mar.
Unattributed. J. Walter Thompson Radio Programs 1930 Apr.
Unattributed. J. Walter Thompson, 1847-1928 1928 Nov.
Unattributed. Just What Effect Does Weather Have on Retail Sales? 1927 Mar.
Unattributed. Keeping Peace With Mass Production 1925 Jan.
Unattributed. Magazine Circulations Among Industrial Employees 1926 Jan.
Unattributed. Management--The Third Ingredient 1927 Feb.
Unattributed. Manhattan's Lunch Time Population 1926 July
Unattributed. Mariemont [a planned community in Cincinatti] 1926 Sept.
Unattributed. Market for Electricity and Electrical Devices 1922 Nov.
Unattributed. Mid-Census Estimate Places Population of United States at 113,000,000 as of July 1, 1925 1926 June
Unattributed. More Automobiles Than Telephones 1924 July
Unattributed. Mr. Groom Addresses Jewelers 1922 Sept.
Unattributed. Nearly Thirteen Million Americans Live in Villages 1926 Nov.
Unattributed. Net Profits of General Motors Double Ford's for 1926 1927 May
Unattributed. New Evidence on Brand Consciousness 1923 Apr.
Unattributed. New Figures Supplementing Population and Its Distribution 1924 Oct.
Unattributed. New J. Walter Thompson Company Office on the Pacific Coast (San Francisco) 1923 July
Unattributed. New Organizations of Advertising Men 1923 Aug.
Unattributed. Note on the Increase of American Investments Abroad 1925 Oct.
Unattributed. Number of Domestic Servants in U,S, Decreases 350,000 in Ten Years 1925 Sept.
Unattributed. Out-Britishing the Britisher 1928 Nov.
Unattributed. Paul T. Cherington Joins the Staff 1922 May
Unattributed. Pool Versus the Chain Store 1922 Nov.
Unattributed. Population and Its Distribution Helps the Government Solve a Problem 1922 Feb.
Unattributed. Population Figures for Great Britain and Ireland 1924 July
Unattributed. President Coolidge Sees in Advertising a Great Educational Force 1927 Jan.
Unattributed. President of Large Insurance Company Endorses Dr. Watson's Plan 1922 Feb.
Unattributed. Prestige and Good Will Protected by Sweeping Injunction 1922 Apr.
Unattributed. Purpose of the Essay Contest 1922 Oct.
Unattributed. Recent Distinguished Visitors to the New York Office 1922 July
Unattributed. Retail Shopping Areas Wins Book Award for Advertising Research 1928 Mar.
Unattributed. Second International Silk Exposition 1923 Mar.
Unattributed. Selling the Hospital Field 1923 Apr.
Unattributed. Seventy Years of Growth 1924 Nov.
Unattributed. Shopping Center for Three Nations 1927 May
Unattributed. Size of the Market for Heating Specialties Little Appreciated 1923 Apr.
Unattributed. Some Grocery Chain Store Figures 1924 Oct.
Unattributed. Some New Developments in Commercial Statistics 1925 Oct.
Unattributed. Steady Increase in Purchasing Power of Consumer 1925 Sept.
Unattributed. Study of Magazine Circulation in Cincinnati, Ohio 1923 Oct.
Unattributed. Subject of the Essay Contest 1922 Nov.
Unattributed. The Advance Has Come Through Substituting Observation for Preconceptions & Passions 1926 July
Unattributed. The Automobile Industry in Nearer Certainty Than at any Previous Time 1927 Feb.
Unattributed. The Creative Plus Which No One Mind By Itself Could Achieve 1926 Nov.
Unattributed. Transplanting a New England Farm House to the Heart of New York City 1922 Feb.
Unattributed. Under the Bushel? [making ideas graphic] 1922 Feb.
Unattributed. Value of a Window Display Not Wholly Dependent on Its Dignity 1922 Dec.
Unattributed. We Are Still Laying Bricks Like the Babylonians 1926 June
Unattributed. What Do Our Rural Neighbors Buy? (Putnam Co., N.Y., and Randolph Co., Ind.) 1926 Mar.
Unattributed. What is Happening to the Thirteen Thousand Villages 1927 Sept.
Unattributed. When Sampling Increased Sales 30 Times 1922 July
Unattributed. White Motor Trucks Utilize Irving Advertisement 1922 Mar.
Unattributed. Who Does Not Seek After Persuasion? 1925 Oct.
Unattributed. Why a Study of Purchasing Power is Important 1924 Mar.
Unattributed. Will the Automobile Break Down International Boundaries? 1927 Apr.
Advertisements. Baker's Coconut (Franklin Baker Co.) 1923 Mar.
Advertisements. Barreled Sunlight (U.S. Gutta Percha Paint Co.) 1922 Aug.
Advertisements. Buick (General Motors, London) 1928 Nov.
Advertisements. Cheramy Perfume 1922 May
Advertisements. Collier's 1922 Oct.
Advertisements. Davey Tree Surgeons 1923 Apr.
Advertisements. Eagle-A Bond (Amer. Writing Paper Co.) 1922 June
Advertisements. Gruen Watches 1923 Jan.
Advertisements. J. Walter Thompson Company's Prize Essay Contest 1922 Aug.
Advertisements. Keds Shoes (U.S. Rubber Co.) 1922 Sept.
Advertisements. Lux Flakes for Dishwashing 1923 Mar.; 1922 Oct..
Advertisements. O'Sullivan Heels 1922 July
Advertisements. Pebeco Tooth Paste 1923 Feb.
Advertisements. Pennsylvania Railroad 1927 Feb.
Advertisements. Phenix Cheese Co. 1922 Nov.
Advertisements. Rice's Slices Bread 1929 Oct.
Advertisements. Richardson Roofing 1923 Mar.
Advertisements. Savage Arms Corp. (rifles) 1922 Oct.
Advertisements. Sunbrite Cleanser (Swift & Co.) 1923 Mar.
Advertisements. Swift's Ham and Bacon 1922 Dec.
Advertisements. Vanity Fair Silk Underwear 1922 Dec.
Advertisements. Woodbury's Soap (Andrew Jergens Co.) 1922 Dec.
News Bulletin Contents by Title
Materials located in Boxes MN1-MN5.
2nd Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Apr.
A House in the Country. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Nov.
Achievements of the Automobile. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Aug.
Advertising Adventures in France. [Author: Cody, E. Morrill] 1923 June
Advertising and American Prosperity. [Author: Mazur, Paul] 1928 May
Advertising and the Cost of Distribution. [Author: Stanton, Henry T.] 1927 June
Advertising as a Career. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1927 May
Advertising By Radio. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1923 May
Advertising Illustration in England. [Author: Aymar, Gordon C.] 1929 Apr.
Advertising Manager--A Business Man or Technician?. [Author: Smith, Guy C.] 1929 Dec.
Advertising Principles Applied to International Politics. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Jan.
Advertising Revenue Twice That from Subscription Sales. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Mar.
Aims and Responsibilities of the Business School. [Author: David, Donald Kirk] 1927 Mar.
Ambassadors of Commerce. [Author: Flower, H.C.] 1930 Apr.
American Dollar Replaces the Gold Standard. [Author: McKenna, Reginald] 1928 Mar.
American Farmer, Inc.. [Author: Smith, Harlan] 1922 Oct.
American Manufacturer Meets His Foreign Consumer. [Author: Miner, Henry C.] 1929 Oct.
American Manufacturers Find a Market in Lithuania. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Jan.
Analysis of Building Volume. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Feb.
Ancient Art and Modern Industry. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Apr.
...And You Meet Such Interesting People. [Author: Faulkner, George H.] 1930 Apr.
Are American Manufacturers Foolish Exporters?. [Author: Wyman, Walter A.] 1922 Dec.
Are Booklets Read and Kept?. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1922 Sept.
Are the Makers of Automotive Accessories on the Horns of a Sales Dilemma?. [Author: Ashby, Bruce] 1927 Feb.
Art Sources Investigated. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Apr.
Association Advertising. [Author: Legler, Henry] 1929 Apr.
At Last--A Boon to the Inventor. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Aug.
Automobile Registrations Jump Two Millions in 1924. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Feb.
Automobile Saturation?. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 July
Baker's Coconut (Franklin Baker Co.). [Advertisement] 1923 Mar.
Barreled Sunlight (U.S. Gutta Percha Paint Co.). [Advertisement] 1922 Aug.
Be Yourself! But Can You?. [Author: Anderson, Hayward] 1929 Dec.
Beech-Nut Case. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Feb.
Behind the Doorbell. [Author: Henderson, Howard] 1923 Aug.
Bertand Russell on Behaviorism. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Jan.
Bit of Old New England in a New York Office Building. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Jan.
Brass Tacks in Foreign Trade. [Author: Hutchison, James L.] 1923 Feb.
Britain Now Has 562 Millionaires. [Author: Unattributed] 1928 May
British Courts Render Interesting Decision on Advertising. [Author: Unattributed] 1928 May
British Papers Boost Their Circulation With Free Insurance. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 June
Brooklyn Retailers Seek Court Order to Compel Push-Cart Vendors to Trade in ront of Their Stores. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Sept.
Buick (General Motors, London). [Advertisement] 1928 Nov.
Bunk. [Author: Holmes, Mildred] 1929 Aug.
C.M. Olmstead Joins the Staff. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Apr.
Can Advertising Cripple Manufacturing and Selling Resourcefulness?. [Author: Day, William L.] 1929 Aug.
Can Advertising Effects Be Measured?. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 Apr.
Cement Shortage Threatens. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Nov.
Chain Stores in the Grocery Business. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 Sept.
Changing Markets. [Author: Harcourt, Alfred] 1930 May
Character and Unity from Hidden Technique. [Author: De Vries, John T.] 1922 Mar.
Cheramy Perfume. [Advertisement] 1922 May
[Cherington] Will Head Subcommittee on Census of Distribution. [Author: Mims, Stewart L.] 1922 Mar.
Chicago Office Goes Pyrenees. [Author: Parker, Dorothy] 1929 Dec.
Clients of the J. Walter Thompson Company. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 (Mar., May, July, Sept., Nov.); 1923 (Jan., Mar., May, July, Nov.); 1924 (Jan., July, Oct.); 1925 (July-Oct., Dec.); 1926 (Jan., Apr., June, July, Sept., Nov.); 1927 (Jan.-June, Sept.); 1928 (Mar., May, July, Nov.); 1929 (Mar., Apr., Aug., Dec.); 193
College Education for Business. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1925 Aug.
Collier's. [Advertisement] 1922 Oct.
Columnist Views Modern Merchandising. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Sept.
Come Back of the Auto Industry. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 May
Competition of Canadian and American Magazines in Canada. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Apr.
Complex Art of Being Simple. [Author: Hutchison, James L.] 1923 Mar.
Consumers Decide. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 July
Consumer's Purchasing Power in Thirty-one Cities. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Nov.
Contestants Busy on Essay. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Jan.
Contributions from Budget Studies to the Construction of a Statistical Index of the Purchasing Power of Consumers in the United States. [Author: Winslow, Emma A.] 1924 Mar.
Control of the Advertising Appropriation. [Author: Young, James W.] 1922 Feb.
Convention of the A.A.C. of W.. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 July
Co-operative Advertising. [Author: Young, James W.] 1926 Nov.
Coue Was Right. [Author: Leffingwell, Albert] 1923 May
Cutting Down Waste in Store Display. [Author: Webb, Ewing T.] 1922 May
Davey Tree Surgeons. [Advertisement] 1923 Apr.
Department Store Costs of Business. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Oct.
Development of Advertising With Distribution. [Author: Raymond, C.E.] 1922 Oct.
Development of Outdoor Advertising. [Author: Perrin, E.O.] 1922 Feb.
Discussion of Business Policies Appropriate to Present Economic Conditions. [Author: Clark, Earle] 1923 Nov.
Distinguished British Physician Tells of Progress in the Mastery of Disease. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Nov.
Distribution Census and Trends in Retailing. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1929 Oct.
Do Busy Men Read Advertisements?. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 June
Do Your Salesmen Use Your Advertising?. [Author: Walker, David N.] 1923 Aug.
Dollar-A-Year Graduate School. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1929 Aug.
Dr, Klein Optimistic as to Export Market. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 Sept.
Eagle-A Bond (Amer. Writing Paper Co.). [Advertisement] 1922 June
Economic Marketing. [Author: Barnes, Julius H.] 1925 Mar.
Economic Phases of Advertising. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 June
Editorial Character of Business Papers. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1926 Jan.
Effectiveness of Various Sizes of Advertising Space. [Author: Perrin, E.O.] 1922 Oct.
Elementary Methods in Selecting Newspaper Media. [Author: Pearson, George] 1922 June
Eloquence in Advertising Illustration. [Author: De Vries, John T.] 1922 Feb.